<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BEM API Reference on Bots By RevenYOU</title>
    <link>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BEM API Reference on Bots By RevenYOU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Orders</title>
      <link>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/orders/</guid>
      <description>The Order endpoints allow your bot to enter, monitor and cancel orders directly.
When entering an order, the bot must provide a unique id. In addition, once the order is accepted by the platform, a unique id will be generated by BEM. Both ids may be used to reference the order.
[POST] placeOrder Description Place an order on the platform.
Parameters (Body)
   Name Type Description Mandatory     signalProvider string Name of the Bot Yes   signalProviderKey string Secret key Yes   extId string Unique ID generated by bot Yes   exchange string Target exchange for the order Yes   baseAsset string Base asset of the order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signals</title>
      <link>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/signals/</guid>
      <description>The Signal endpoints enable your bot to send and manage signals. A signal is a mini-strategy that allows your bot to define an entry point, close targets and stop-loss level. BEM will generate the corresponding orders and send them to the exchange at the appropriate time.
[POST] placeSignal Description Send a signal to the platform
Parameters (Body)
   Name Type Description Mandatory     signalProvider string Name of the Bot Yes   signalProviderKey string Secret key Yes   extId string Unique ID generated by bot Yes   exchange string Target exchange for the order Yes   baseAsset string Base asset of the order Yes   quoteAsset string Quote asset of the order Yes   direction string &amp;lsquo;buy2sell&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;sell2buy&amp;rsquo; Yes   openLimitPrice string The level at which to open the position Yes   openQtyPct string The percentage of available asset to use Yes   openQtyAbs string Absolute value to use Only Internal   openTtlType string Time To Last type for the opening order, &amp;lsquo;gtc&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;secs&amp;rsquo; Yes   openTtlSecs string Time To Last seconds Yes if type = &amp;lsquo;secs&amp;rsquo;   closeTargets [CloseTarget] Array of CloseTargets Yes   closeTtlType string Time to Last type for close orders, &amp;lsquo;gtc&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;secs&amp;rsquo; Yes   closeTtlSecs string Time to Last seconds if type = &amp;lsquo;secs&amp;rsquo; Yes if type = &amp;lsquo;secs&amp;rsquo;   slLimitPricePct string Stoploss order limit as pct of openLimitPrice (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/faq/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between Base- and Quote asset? The baseAsset of an order or signal is the asset that will be bought or sold. The quoteAsset is the asset that will be paid (when buying the base asset) or received (when selling the base asset). So, the below order body describes an order to buy BTC with a limit price of 47000 USDT. Selling BTC for USDT only requires the side of the order to be changed; no switching of base- and quoteAsset is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Positions</title>
      <link>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://revenyouio.github.io/bots-docs/positions/</guid>
      <description>To get an overview of the different asset positions of a bot, use the getBotAssetsPct endpoint.
[GET] getBotAssetsPct Description Get an overview of the (relative) asset positions of a bot.
Parameters (Body)
   Name Type Description Mandatory     signalProvider string Name of the Bot Yes   signalProviderKey string Secret key Yes   exchange string  Yes   baseAsset string  Yes    Example curl -X &amp;#39;GET&amp;#39; \  &amp;#39;https://signal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
